nippon.com 2014-04-15

# Privacy Policy | Nippon.com

#### Overview

As the operator of Nippon.com, the Nippon Communications Foundation (“we”) may collect information from users as necessary for the operation of the services provided by the website. The information acquired is at all times handled appropriately within the scope of the purposes of use.

#### Information Acquisition and Use

We automatically collect and store data including Internet domain names, IP addresses, and other information on access to this website. This information is used as reference data aiding the operation of the services provided by this website.

We collect email addresses provided voluntarily by users subscribing to the email update service (currently being prepared). This information is used to send the requested information to the users.

We also collect names and email addresses from users who voluntarily provide this information via the “Contact” section of this website. This personal data may be used when replying to users who have contacted us via this function.

#### Limitations

With the exception of cases of legal disclosure requests; cases of illegal access, threats, or other unlawful acts; or other special reasons, we will not use the information acquired for any purposes other than those described above, nor will it be provided to any third party. However, statistical information regarding access to this website or non-identifying information on users’ attributes may be made public.

#### Data Security

We take all measures necessary to manage acquired information appropriately to prevent the leakage, loss, or destruction of the information described above.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

We never collect full names, dates of birth, or any other information that would permit the identification of an individual user. For this reason, we cannot respond to requests for disclosure of personal information from users of the email update service (currently being prepared). It is possible at any time for users to unsubscribe from this service and remove their email addresses from our records, or to change their registered email address to another one.

The “Contact” section of this website allows users to voluntarily provide an email address. We will use this information only to reply to the user’s query. We are unable to respond to requests for release of information provided by a user, or to revise or delete information once it has been submitted by a user, due to the lack of identification procedures that would allow confirmation that the requester is that user.

#### Disclaimer

We provide information on Nippon.com while taking every possible care in its production. We assume no legal liability for the completeness, accuracy, usefulness, security, or any other characteristic of the content of this website. We are not responsible for any consequences whatsoever that may result from decisions or actions taken by users based on the information on the website.

This Privacy Policy is applicable only to the Nippon.com website and the information contained therein.
